hi hi hi it's your boy Stephen Blake and
welcome back to the channel and yes as
you saw from the video title we are
doing another product review I'm pretty
fired up about this one I'm not even
gonna lie a huge thank you to my friends
over at kettle and fire for getting me
the major hookup here we got six
different packages they sent to me for
times sake and as you know I like to try
and keep these product reviews sweet and
short so I'm only gonna choose one
package to go over in terms of the
macros ingredients price and then the
taste test you already know the drill so
let's just kick it so the flavour I
chose is the classic chicken bone broth
I'm very much so a plain-jane myself but
I must say that I do love myself a good
bone broth especially when it has the
chicken in it
the apoyo as most of you call it 10
grams of protein collagen source made
with organic free-range chicken bones 14
plus hours slow and simmer organic
chicken bones simmer and sip you could
say it's bagged the bone but in a good
way okie dokie artichokie
let's jump into the ingredients organic
chicken bone broth water organic chicken
bones organic onions organic carrots
organic fennel organic leeks apple cider
vinegar time shitake mushroom
tamarind extract organic bay leaf
vegetable broth you guys get the idea
lots of organic don't see anything crazy
out of the ordinary when it comes to the
ingredients here pretty run-of-the-mill
easy straight stuff now let's jump into
the macros so two serving size per
container serving size 1 cup 245 grams
amount per serving 45 calories total fat
0 grams saturated fat 0 grams trans fat
0 grams cholesterol 0 milligrams sodium
170 milligrams total carb diet' a fiber
0 grams total sugars zero gram protein
10 gram macros look a ok to me too as
well total carbohydrates
one gram so that minus the zero dietary
fiber would just be one gram of total
carbohydrate no added sugar very
importante there no fat no saturated fat
no trans fat surprised there's no fat
though because I would think that
especially when it comes from the bones
the bones would usually have some sort
of fat content but that's just me I
guess thinking out loud on that one now
this is actually where it gets a little
bit tricky with the price because some
companies sell their bone broths in
different variant sizes when it comes to
the packs for the sake of this review
though I actually only picked kit on
fire because it comes in a three pack
and then the other two brands just one
single container and then our third
brand is actually a twelve pack so for
the pack of three here with kettle on
fire as actually going to be seventeen
ounces per container of each one so
seventeen times three I was going to
come out to around once a fifty one
fluid ounces total and that's actually
gonna cost you about twenty three ninety
seven which is about I want to say
twenty six twenty seven bucks give or
take and that would actually round out
to nine dollars per container
the second bone broth brand I selected
is called bonafide and that is only ten
dollars for twenty four fluid ounces and
that comes in just one big pack so I
would be around I want to say roughly
thirteen fourteen bucks
once you finish totaling everything then
the third brand I found was called
Pacific foods and they actually are the
12-pack brand that I mentioned so that
is actually going to be twenty two
dollars and fifteen cents for a pack of
twelve and the amount in each pack is
only going to be eight fluid ounces but
when you multiply the 12 times eight and
you get 96 ounces total of bone broth so
after going over the prices I think I
would just have a few quick takeaways
one of them being that Pacific foods is
only going to have one flavor for that
twelve pack so I do personally think
that you get more bang for your buck
using Pacific foods is brand and bone
broth but on the flip side with kettle
and Fire you get three different flavors
for that three pack I really think it's
all depending upon your choice and
preference at the end of the day but I
do think just for my personal opinion
from
kind of reviewing everything you would
get more like I said bang for your buck
going with Pacific foods hopefully the
pricing for this makes sense it was a
little bit tricky for me to just kind of
decipher it on my end but I think I did
a pretty good job and now it's time for
the taste test and as most of you know
bone broth is supposed to be drinking at
a hot or a warm temperature but me being
me and the weird person that I am I am
going to just drink this as is straight
out of the container
I don't want to spill how do you open
this
Oh tear along dotted line after
squeezing corners actually read more I
got it oh no I spilled it tastes
differently when it's not hot I will say
that much oh geez hello hello I think
there's mushrooms in this I'm not a huge
mushroom fan I think it tastes good I'm
like bone rough granted I think it
tastes them differently when you're sick
not so much when you're as well okay
let's run it back on this video and
recap what we just went over ingredients
love them lots of organic stuff
nothing crazy out of the ordinary very
straightforward run-of-the-mill stuff
macro time love those as well only one
gram of carbohydrates and the serving
size for what it's worth I think is
great as well now let's go over the
price I do think that if you enjoy
variety and you want different flavors
go with kettle and fire but I think that
if you want just more like I said
longevity specific foods bonafide I
think is the same amount in fluid ounces
if you doubled it from the 24 ounces to
the 48 ounces which would come out to
the 40 ounces you'd get from a variety
pack of three and four the taste tastes
like regular bone broth I think that for
me though just because there was
mushrooms in there I'm not a huge
mushroom fan I just never have I had a
really bad experience as a kid and
mushrooms pyramid scarred me for life
and that's pretty much it as always
thanks you guys so much for watching I
appreciate all the love and support be
sure you guys smash that like button
comment down below and check back every
week for brand new product new videos
just like this one and really quickly if
I may just shameless
we plugged my patron on page it's a
little way for you guys to get back to
me I kind of think of it like a virtual
tip jar of sorts but there's definitely
no obligation at all to give but if you
have a few extra dollars lying around
then you know hey throw my way all right
that's all I got
see you guys later